<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HeartRateApp</string>

    <string name="normal_low_rate_hint">Your heart rate is Low. Apart from being a highly trained athlete, a slow heart rate is usually caused by an underlying issue. Work with your doctor or another healthcare practitioner to find and treat the cause.</string>
    <string name="normal_normal_rate_hint">Your heart rate is Normal. A typical heart rate in this state is for adults is 60–100 bpm. You can prevent out of normal by doing the following: regular exercise, reducing stress, maintaining a healthy weight, and eating healthy.</string>
    <string name="normal_high_rate_hint">Your heart rate is High. Take a walk outside, ideally in nature. Relaxation exercises such as controlled breathing, meditation. To prevent this condition, practice yoga and stretching.</string>
    <string name="exercise_low_rate_hint">Your heart rate is Low. You should adjust your training plan to be more effective. Work with your doctor or another healthcare practitioner to find and treat the cause.</string>
    <string name="exercise_normal_rate_hint">Your heart rate is Normal. You can prevent out of normal by doing the following: regular exercise, reducing stress, maintaining a healthy weight, and eating healthy.</string>
    <string name="exercise_high_rate_hint">Your heart rate is High. It\'s advisable to should slow down or stop exercising and discuss it further with your physician or cardiologist. This may be a sign of serious illness.</string>

    <string name="empty_reports_title">"Here you can see your reports.\nTry your first measurement."</string>
    <string name="empty_statistics_title">"Here you can view your statistics.\nTry the first measurement."</string>

    <string name="squats_workout_title">Squats</string>
    <string name="squats_workout_description">1. Stand with feet shoulder-width apart and hands clasped in front of chest, elbows slightly bent.\n2. Brace abs, push hips back, and bend knees, lowering body into a squat. Pause at the bottom, then push back up to the starting position.</string>
    <string name="plank_workout_title">Forearm Plank</string>
    <string name="plank_workout_description">1. Lie face down with your legs extended, elbows bent directly under your shoulders, and your palms flat on the floor.\n2. Engage your abs, press the floor away from yourself with your forearms. You should form a straight line from shoulders to heels.</string>
    <string name="rope_workout_title">Jump Rope</string>
    <string name="rope_workout_description">Swing the rope over your head and jump as it passes your feet. You don\'t have to jump high, just enough to clear the rope. Land evenly on the balls of both feet.</string>
    <string name="step_workout_title">Step-Ups</string>
    <string name="step_workout_description">To begin, stand behind your platform. Place one foot on top of the surface, pressing into your heel as you step up. Bring your other foot up to meet the first on top of the platform. Return your second foot to the floor, followed by the first.</string>
    <string name="biceps_workout_title">Biceps Curl</string>
    <string name="biceps_workout_description">1. Stand with your feet shoulder-width apart and a dumbbell in each hand.\n2. Turn your arms to face forward and bend your elbows to move the dumbbells up toward your shoulders. Slowly raise both dumbbells up, after slowly lower the dumbbells.</string>

</resources>